# ALWASI MUHRIJAFIATNA

# **Electrical Engineering Education Bachelor**

Bandung | +62 8953 5976 598 | <u>alwasiwasi29@gmail.com</u> | alwasim.github.io | Instagram/alwasi\_mf | linkedin.com/in/alwasi-muhrijafiatna-757b9a27b/



### **SUMMARY**

A Fresh Graduate from Faculty of Engineering and Industrial Education in Indonesia University of Education graduated with cum laude honors and very interested in field of AI programming and Electrical Telecommunication with a total of 3 year experience as an aviation electronics student at SMKN 12 Bandung. Obtained competency certification in the field of electronics and has participated in internship at PT Hutama Karya as MEP Engineering, Industrial Work Practice with aviation maintenance expertise at PT Dewata Angkasa, Industrial Work Practice with Arduino programming at PT Inovindo Digital Media, Teacher in Aircraft Electronic Navigation Communication Installation Subject at SMKN 12 bandung, and has a license The Proficiency of English to Speakers of Other Languages from The Language Center, Indonesia University of Education. Has alongside excellent communication skills and pleasant personality.

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### PT HUTAMA KARYA

MEP Engineer (February 2024 – March 2024)

- Verify installation MEP has correct as shop drawing.
- Mapping progress installation of mechanical, electrical, plumbing, and fire system on project.

#### SMKN 12 Bandung

Teacher (July 2023 – December 2023)

- Teaching in two Class with concentration of aviation electronics.
- Teaching Aircraft Electronic Navigation Communication Installation and Installation of Instrument in Aircraft subject.
- Make a learning plan
- Crate a module for student to learn.
- Create student worksheet.
- Conduct assessments on students.

#### PT INOVINDO DIGITAL MEDIA

Apprentice Programmer (June 2023 – Augst 2023)

- Making an IoT (Internet of Things) Project.
- Design and Build an IoT-based smart pot system to optimize the growth and care of ornamental plants.

• Make a module about design and build an IoT-based smart pot system to optimize the growth and care of ornamental plants.

#### PT DEWATA ANGKASA

Apprentice Electrician (April 2019 – July 2019)

- Checking and testing of each repair unit.
- Trial and error of generator unit, hydraulic unit, and instrument aviation unit until find cause the malfunction based on manual book.
- Maintenance, repair, and overhaul of hydraulic system and instrument of aircraft.

### **EDUCATION**

#### INDONESIA UNIVERSITY OF EDUCATION

Bachelor of Education (Electrical Engineering)

- Temporary GPA 3.54 (2020 Present)
  - Actively participation of organization and training.
  - Participated in more than 10+ campus event, such as skills training, workshop, and webinars.

# VOCATIONAL HIGH SCHOOL 12 BANDUNG - Bandung, West Java

Aviation Electronics (2017 - 2020)

• Graduated with average score of all subject 85.

# **PROJECTS**

Application of Machine Learning and Deep Learning for Horticultural Plants Identification web Based (April 2024 – September 2024)

• Created a web based application to identify a horticulture plants, weeds, pest, and make a estimated cost to cultivate a crop.

Design and Development of IoT-based smart pot system to optimize the growth and care of ornamental plants (June 2023 – Augst 2023)

• Created a pot that can analyze the condition of a plant based IoT Cloud.

Design of FTTH Access Network Using Gigabit Passive Optical Network (GPON) in Setiabudhi Terrace Housing Estate (April 2023 – May 2023)

Created the design of Fiber to the home (FTTH) network for 45 house in Setiabudhi
Terrace Housing Estate.

Simple Hartley Oscillator Resonance Frequency Calculator (March 2023 – April 2023)

• Created a simple calculator with three inputs using python language

Design and Development of Automatic Trash Bin Based on IoT (May 2020 – June 2020)

• Created a miniature IoT based automatic gate using an ESP32 microcontroller, and ultrasonic sensor to measure the distance between hands and a trash bin.

### **SKILLS**

Electrical Telecommunication, Electrical Installation, Leadership and Communication, Arduino IDE, HTML, CSS, MySQL, Microsoft Visual Studio Code, AutoCAD, Microsoft Office 365, Machine Learning Applications, Python Programming. Proteus, NI Multisims.

### **ORGANIZATION**

## Himpunan Mahasiswa Elektro

Chairman of the Sub-Division of Telecommunication Engineering Development (June 2022 – June 2023)

• Creating a plan and instruction the employee to carry out the work program

Steering Committee Telecommunication Training (January 2023 – May 2023)

 Provided actionable recommendations to the committee on how to optimize event planning process, resulting in a 20% increase in attendance and a 30% reduction in event planning time.

Project Manager Workshop Telecommunication (September 2021 – February 2022)

 Directing and ensuring the Committee prepares and carries out the work program until completion.

### LICENSE & CERTIFICATE

For more information of license and certificate, you can access link of below:

https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1FHngS2gjBjLzGSmA07h01 gz9Q4gGd0Y